epson.net 2007-12-25

# Epson Corporate

Seiko Epson Corp. ("Epson") respects user privacy on our web sites. Epson abides by a strict compliance program for collecting or using personal data protection, and this compliance program is continually being improved to ensure the protection of any and all private information. This privacy policy is designed to provide specific information about the privacy and data collection practices for the site: [www.epson.co.jp/e](http://www.epson.co.jp/e/).

**Disclaimer**  
This Privacy Policy is applicable to Japan, where the server for this website resides. Other Epson sites not managed by Seiko Epson and Epson sites in other countries may operate under their own privacy policies.

**Identifying Information**  
In general, you can visit this website without telling us who you are or providing any information about yourself. In some areas of the Site, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to support our relationship with you, such as to enable you to sign up for a mailing list, or follow up with you. Epson asks for identifying information when you:

  1. Want to contact Epson to ask for information.
  2. Participate in a sweepstakes, or other promotional offer.
  3. Register to receive mailings, or e-mail notification about press releases & newsletters.

In these instances, Epson will ask for your name, e-mail address, or other appropriate information needed to provide you with these services. In all instances, it will be clear to you that you are submitting this type of information. In addition, if you choose to receive a newsletter or other mailing from us, you will always be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings as described in the Opting-Out section below.

**What Epson Will Do With Your Information**  
If you choose to give us personal information for any of the purposes above, this information is retained by Epson and is used by Epson only to support your relationship with us.

**What Others May Do With Your Information**  
Epson does not share, rent, or sell any personally identifying information provided through the Site (such as your name or email address) to any outside organization for use in its marketing or solicitations. From time to time Epson may use third party agents or contractors who will have access to your personal information to perform services for Epson (such as a database management service) but only in accordance with this stated privacy policy. And Epson requires certain safeguards in place by any vendors with access to personal data collected by Epson, including a written commitment to keep the information confidential and to only use the data to carry out the services for Epson. In addition, Epson may also share aggregate information about its customers and its web site visitors to advertisers, business partners, and other third parties. For example, we might share that our users are x percent PC users and y percent Macintosh users. None of this information, however, will contain personal, identifying information about any of our users.

**Opting Out**  
If you have registered for the press release and/or newsletter mailing list, and would like to opt-out, simply visit the following site: 

. To unsubscribe, fill out the form and choose the "Unsubscribe from the mail service" option.

**Collecting Aggregate Data and Cookies**  
Like many web sites, Epson collects non-personal data about how the site is being viewed. Most non-personal data is collected via cookies or other analysis technologies. The Site includes analysis features which enable Epson to capture aggregate data about how the site is used, such as the amount of total traffic, the number of page views or the number of unique visitors. This feature does not capture personal identifying information about any visitors to the Site. Epson reviews this data and uses it only for internal purposes of assessing and for managing the Site. Epson uses cookies on our site to make the user experience better. A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a website to your computer's hard drive. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information, but we may use the cookies to identify your computer.

**Children's Privacy Protection**  
Epson is aware of the heightened need to protect the privacy of children under the age of 16. The vast majority of the material on the Site is not intended for children and is not targeted to children under the age of 16. Epson does not knowingly collect data from children and, if we learn that we have received personal data from a child, we will remove this information from our database.

**Third Party Links**  
This website does provide links to other sites. Other Internet sites and services have their own privacy and data collection practices. Please note that once you click on one of these sites, you leave the Epson Site and Epson has no control or responsibility for the privacy policies or data collection activities at another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements at those sites as you visit them.

**Changes to this Policy**  
Epson may from time to time revise its privacy policy. We will not, however, use your existing information in a manner not previously disclosed. You will be advised and have the opportunity to opt out of any new use of your information.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the Site, you can use the following form to e-mail Epson:  
Revised November 2005
